<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scratch Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/</link><description>Recent content on Scratch Addons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://scratchaddons.com/nb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Send tilbakemelding</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/feedback/</guid><description>Send tilbakemelding Have something to say about Scratch Addons? Let us know through this feedback form.
window.i18nStrings = { statusSending: 'Sending...', statusSuccess: 'Sent! Thanks for the feedback.', statusFailed: 'Something went wrong. Try sending again?' } Scratch username, or other identifiers (optional) Feedback Send list of my currently enabled addons (recommended) Send Alternatives In case you need an alternative, here are some choices.</description></item><item><title>Utvidelser</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/addons/</guid><description>Utvidelser This page lists all of the addons that are implemented on Scratch Addons.
This page is incomplete, and we need your help to complete the images. Read more here.
List view In this page, an easter egg addon will have an egg symbol besides its name.' data-toggle="tooltip" data-placement="left" data-html="true"Easter egg 2D color picker 2d-color-picker Replaces saturation and brightness sliders in the costume editor with a 2D color picker.</description></item><item><title>Velkommen!</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/nb/welcome/</guid><description>Velkommen! Scratch Addons has been installed successfully!
Thank you for installing. We hope you enjoy the extension!
Getting started Step 1 Click the Scratch Addons extension icon It is on the top-right corner of your browser. Google Chrome users need to click the puzzle icon to find the icon.
Step 2 Press the gear icon to go to the Settings page This will open the Settings page where you can configure how the extension works.</description></item></channel></rss>