<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scratch Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/</link><description>Recent content on Scratch Addons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://scratchaddons.com/hu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/docs/getting-started/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/docs/getting-started/quick-start/</guid><description>Telepítés Let&amp;rsquo;s get started by installing Scratch Addons. Scratch Addons is available in both Chrome Web Store and Add-ons for Firefox.
Chrome Web Store (for Google Chrome and other Chromium-based browsers) Add-ons for Firefox (for Mozilla Firefox) Elkezdés To get started, you need to access the settings page of the addon to see the functions of it.
Locate Scratch Addons on the toolbar and click it.</description></item><item><title>Telepítés</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/docs/getting-started/installing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/docs/getting-started/installing/</guid><description>From extension stores Scratch Addons is available in both Chrome Web Store and Add-ons for Firefox.
Chrome Web Store (for Google Chrome, Opera, Brave, Vivaldi, Microsoft Edge (&amp;gt;79), and other Chromium-based browsers)
https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/fbeffbjdlemaoicjdapfpikkikjoneco Add-ons for Firefox (for Mozilla Firefox)
https://addons.mozilla.org/firefox/addon/scratch-messaging-extension/ From source About GitHub releases The releases page contains the code and installation files for all development builds of Scratch Addons, as well as the mirror of the store builds.</description></item><item><title>Kiegészítők</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/addons/</guid><description>Kiegészítők Ez az oldal felsorolja az összes kiegészítőt, amik már felkerültek a Scratch Addons-ra.
This page is incomplete, and we need your help to complete the images. Read more here.
List view In this page, an easter egg addon will have an egg symbol besides its name.' data-toggle="tooltip" data-placement="left" data-html="true"Easter egg 2D color picker 2d-color-picker Replaces saturation and brightness sliders in the costume editor with a 2D color picker.</description></item><item><title>Nem támogatott böngésző</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/unsupported-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/unsupported-browser/</guid><description>Nem támogatott böngésző Scratch Addons doesn't support the browser you're using. Use updated versions of Chrome, Firefox, or other browsers based on them to get started:
Chromium 80+ Chrome 80+ Download How to update Microsoft Edge 80+ Download How to update Opera 67+ Download How to update Brave 1.3+ Download Vivaldi 2.</description></item><item><title>Visszajelzés küldése</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/feedback/</guid><description>Visszajelzés küldése Have something to say about Scratch Addons? Let us know through this feedback form.
window.i18nStrings = { statusSending: 'Sending...', statusSuccess: 'Sent! Thanks for the feedback.', statusFailed: 'Something went wrong. Try sending again?' } Scratch username, or other identifiers (optional) Feedback Send list of my currently enabled addons (recommended) Send Alternatives In case you need an alternative, here are some choices.</description></item><item><title>Viszlát!</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/farewell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/farewell/</guid><description>Búcsúzunk! A Scratch Addons eltávolítása megtörtént. Köszönjük, hogy használta a bővítményt!
Vissza telepítheti a bővítményt feljebb, a telepítés gombra kattintva . Írhat egy véleményt is a a Chrome-bővítmény oldalán vagy a Firefox-kiegészítő oldalán.
Az ön által megadott eltávolítási indokokon alapozva itt van néhány egyéb dolog amiket még csinálhat.
Problémákba ütközött? Kérjük tudassa velünk itt, vagy készítsen egy GitHub problémátitt. Hiányzik egy jellemző? Mondja el nekünk itt, vagy javasoljon egy probléma készítése által, vagy posztoljon a vitalapunkra.</description></item><item><title>Változási napló</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/changelog/</guid><description>Változtatásnapló Minden megjegyzendő változtatás a projekthez ezen az oldalon fog dokumentálódni.
Note: This changelog is summarised. Check the detailed changelog for all of the changes.
v1.24.3 2022-02-09 Latest ¶ Bug fix: addons not working on forum topics if &amp;ldquo;more forum toolbar buttons&amp;rdquo; addon enabled Bug fix: editor addons sometimes not loaded Links Release page on GitHub Repository state at release Commits made on this version v1.</description></item><item><title>Üdvözöljük!</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/hu/welcome/</guid><description>Üdvözöljük! A Scratch Addons telepítése sikeresen megtörtént!
Köszönjük a telepítést. Reméljük tetszeni fog a bővítmény.
Elkezdés 1. lépés Kattintson a Scratch Addons bővítmény ikonjára A felső jobb sarkában található a böngészőjének. Google Chrome felhasználók valószínűleg rá kell kattintsanak a puzzle ikonra, hogy feljöjjön a Scratch-es ikon.
2. Lépés Nyomja meg a fogaskerék ikont a Beállítások nevű oldalhoz menéshez Ez majd meg fogja nyitni a Beállítások oldalt, ahol konfigurálhatja a bővítmények működését.</description></item></channel></rss>