<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scratch Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/</link><description>Recent content on Scratch Addons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://scratchaddons.com/ro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bun venit</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/welcome/</guid><description>Bun venit Scratch Addons has been installed successfully!
Thank you for installing. We hope you enjoy the extension!
Getting started Step 1 Click the Scratch Addons extension icon It is on the top-right corner of your browser. Google Chrome users need to click the puzzle icon to find the icon.
Step 2 Press the gear icon to go to the Settings page This will open the Settings page where you can configure how the extension works.</description></item><item><title>Extensii</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/addons/</guid><description>Extensii This page lists all of the addons that are implemented on Scratch Addons.
This page is incomplete, and we need your help to complete the images. Read more here.
List view In this page, an easter egg addon will have an egg symbol besides its name.' data-toggle="tooltip" data-placement="left" data-html="true"Easter egg Paletă de culoare 2D 2d-color-picker Replaces saturation and brightness sliders in the costume editor with a 2D color picker.</description></item><item><title>Jurnalul schimbărilor</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/changelog/</guid><description>Jurnalul schimbărilor All notable changes to this project will be documented in this page.
Note: This changelog is summarised. Check the detailed changelog for all of the changes.
v1.24.3 2022-02-09 Latest ¶ Bug fix: addons not working on forum topics if &amp;ldquo;more forum toolbar buttons&amp;rdquo; addon enabled Bug fix: editor addons sometimes not loaded Links Release page on GitHub Repository state at release Commits made on this version v1.</description></item><item><title>La revedere!</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/farewell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/farewell/</guid><description>La revedere! Extensii Scratch a fost dezinstalat. Vă mulțumim pentru că ați folosit extensia.
You may reinstall the extension by clicking the install button above. You can also leave a review on the Chrome extension page or the Firefox addon page.
Based of your reasons of uninstalling the extension, here are some other things that you can do.
Having problems? Please tell us here or create an issue here.</description></item><item><title>Trimite feedback</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/ro/feedback/</guid><description>Trimite feedback Have something to say about Scratch Addons? Let us know through this feedback form.
window.i18nStrings = { statusSending: 'Sending...', statusSuccess: 'Sent! Thanks for the feedback.', statusFailed: 'Something went wrong. Try sending again?' } Scratch username, or other identifiers (optional) Feedback Send list of my currently enabled addons (recommended) Send Alternatives In case you need an alternative, here are some choices.</description></item></channel></rss>