<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scratch Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/id/</link><description>Recent content on Scratch Addons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://scratchaddons.com/id/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Daftar</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/id/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/id/changelog/</guid><description>Daftar All notable changes to this project will be documented in this page.
Note: This changelog is summarised. Check the detailed changelog for all of the changes.
v1.24.3 2022-02-09 Latest ¶ Bug fix: addons not working on forum topics if &amp;ldquo;more forum toolbar buttons&amp;rdquo; addon enabled Bug fix: editor addons sometimes not loaded Links Release page on GitHub Repository state at release Commits made on this version v1.</description></item><item><title>Extension Update (Transition)</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/id/scratch-messaging-transition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/id/scratch-messaging-transition/</guid><description>Ekstensi Scratch Messaging itu sekarang Scratch Addons Apa yang terjadi? Ekstensi Scratch Messaging (oleh griffpatch) telah diperbarui dan sekarang bernama Scratch Addons.
Click the Scratch Addons icon in the extension bar to check out the new redesigned messages summary!
Scratch Addons juga mempunyai banyak fitur terkait Scratch lainnya. Untuk mengaktifkannya, buka pengaturan Scratch Addons. Misalnya, Anda dapat mengaktifkan Scratch Notifier untuk bisa mendapatkan notifikasi browser saat Anda menerima pesan Scratch baru.</description></item><item><title>Kirim Umpan Balik</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/id/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/id/feedback/</guid><description>Kirim Umpan Balik Have something to say about Scratch Addons? Let us know through this feedback form.
window.i18nStrings = { statusSending: 'Sending...', statusSuccess: 'Sent! Thanks for the feedback.', statusFailed: 'Something went wrong. Try sending again?' } Scratch username, or other identifiers (optional) Feedback Send list of my currently enabled addons (recommended) Send Alternatives In case you need an alternative, here are some choices.</description></item></channel></rss>