<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scratch Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/</link><description>Recent content on Scratch Addons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/docs/getting-started/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/docs/getting-started/quick-start/</guid><description>下载中 Let&amp;rsquo;s get started by installing Scratch Addons. Scratch Addons is available in both Chrome Web Store and Add-ons for Firefox.
Chrome Web Store (for Google Chrome and other Chromium-based browsers) Add-ons for Firefox (for Mozilla Firefox) 準備開始 To get started, you need to access the settings page of the addon to see the functions of it.
Locate Scratch Addons on the toolbar and click it.</description></item><item><title>下载中</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/docs/getting-started/installing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/docs/getting-started/installing/</guid><description>From extension stores Scratch Addons is available in both Chrome Web Store and Add-ons for Firefox.
Chrome Web Store (for Google Chrome, Opera, Brave, Vivaldi, Microsoft Edge (&amp;gt;79), and other Chromium-based browsers)
https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/fbeffbjdlemaoicjdapfpikkikjoneco Add-ons for Firefox (for Mozilla Firefox)
https://addons.mozilla.org/firefox/addon/scratch-messaging-extension/ From source About GitHub releases The releases page contains the code and installation files for all development builds of Scratch Addons, as well as the mirror of the store builds.</description></item><item><title>常見問題</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/docs/faq/</guid><description>This page lists frequently asked questions related to the Scratch Addons extension and project.
What is Scratch Addons? Scratch Addons is an &amp;ldquo;all-in-one&amp;rdquo; browser extension for the Scratch website and project editor. It provides features and themes (called addons internally), both for the Scratch website and the project editor. Scratch Addons&amp;rsquo; mission is to combine all existing Scratch extensions, userscripts and userstyles, developed by several members of the Scratch community, into a single easy-to-access place, while still letting users choose which ones to enable.</description></item><item><title>Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/addons/</guid><description>插件 此頁面列出了在 Scratch Addons 上實現的所有插件.
此頁面不完整, 我們需要您的幫助來完成圖像. 閱讀更多這裡
List view In this page, an easter egg addon will have an egg symbol besides its name.' data-toggle="tooltip" data-placement="left" data-html="true"Easter egg 2D color picker 2d-color-picker Replaces saturation and brightness sliders in the costume editor with a 2D color picker. Hold Shift while dragging the cursor to change the values on a single axis.</description></item><item><title>不支持的瀏覽器</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/unsupported-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/unsupported-browser/</guid><description>不支持的瀏覽器 Scratch Addons 不支持您在使用的瀏覽器. Use updated versions of Chrome, Firefox, or other browsers based on them to get started:
Chromium 80+ Chrome 80+ Download How to update Microsoft Edge 80+ Download How to update Opera 67+ Download How to update Brave 1.3+ Download Vivaldi 2.11+ Download How to update 系統要求 Windows 7+ OS X / MacOS 10.</description></item><item><title>发送评价</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/feedback/</guid><description>发送评价 Have something to say about Scratch Addons? Let us know through this feedback form.
window.i18nStrings = { statusSending: 'Sending...', statusSuccess: 'Sent! Thanks for the feedback.', statusFailed: 'Something went wrong. Try sending again?' } Scratch username, or other identifiers (optional) Feedback Send list of my currently enabled addons (recommended) Send Alternatives In case you need an alternative, here are some choices.</description></item><item><title>告別</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/farewell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/farewell/</guid><description>告別 Scratch Addons 已被卸载. 我們非常感謝您使用我們的插件!
You may reinstall the extension by clicking the install button above. You can also leave a review on the Chrome extension page or the Firefox addon page.
Based of your reasons of uninstalling the extension, here are some other things that you can do.
有任何問題嗎? 在这里告訴我們或者在這裡創建問題 A feature is missing? Tell us here or suggest by creating an issue or post about it on our Discussions tab.</description></item><item><title>更改日誌</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/changelog/</guid><description>更改日誌 All notable changes to this project will be documented in this page.
注意： 这个更改日誌是不完整的. 点击这里 可收看所有变化.
v1.24.3 2022-02-09 Latest ¶ Bug fix: addons not working on forum topics if &amp;ldquo;more forum toolbar buttons&amp;rdquo; addon enabled Bug fix: editor addons sometimes not loaded Links Release page on GitHub Repository state at release Commits made on this version v1.24.2 2022-02-07 ¶ Bug fix: &amp;ldquo;clone counter&amp;rdquo; breaking because of incompatibility with some other editor addons Bug fix: &amp;ldquo;debugger&amp;rdquo; feature to highlight the block that triggered a log not working Bug fix: &amp;ldquo;Scratch Notifier&amp;rdquo; playing sound when receiving disabled notification types Bug fix: &amp;ldquo;website dark mode and customizable colors&amp;rdquo; incompatibility with &amp;ldquo;customizable quotes and code blocks on forums&amp;rdquo; Links Release page on GitHub Repository state at release Commits made on this version v1.</description></item><item><title>歡迎</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/zh-tw/welcome/</guid><description>歡迎 Scratch Addons已下载完毕!
Thank you for installing. We hope you enjoy the extension!
準備開始 第一步 点击 Scratch Addons extension的圖標 It is on the top-right corner of your browser. Google Chrome users need to click the puzzle icon to find the icon.
第二步 點擊齒輪的圖標進入設置頁面 This will open the Settings page where you can configure how the extension works.
第三步 Scroll through the addons list and enable the ones that you want You can also configure each of the addons on the bottom section of each addons.</description></item></channel></rss>